I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
-Over there!
-Where?! Where?!
What?
It's a guy!
Hey...When are you gonna
introduce me to your sister?
I see that you're good friends...
Ouch!
Can he really sing?
Well, let's get to the studio
and start our session.
What? We're not going for drinks?
Listen, you...
Oh, well...I guess I'll
just have to belt it out.
I'm looking forward to it.
-Okay, okay. Well, let's go.
-Yeah...
"Hyodo and the Jaguar"
I think I'll get out now.
Yeah...
Won't you come out too, Koyuki?
Koyuki...
You can have this.
Why, this is...
It's the pick that
Eddy of the Dying Breed used.
But...isn't that important to you?
I picked it up at a performance
long ago. It's my treasure.
I can't accept this.
Koyuki...
Take good care of it!
Thanks!
Yeah...
Sorry for calling you out so late at night.
Don't worry about it.
So, what did you want?
I've been thinking about the band,
and I've reached a decision.
And?
I've decided to join Ryusuke's band.
Taira-kun...Are you serious?!
I've always made decisions
based on my instincts.
I've done everything I could...
-It's magic...
-Magic?
Ryusuke's band has the magic
I've been searching for.
See you around, Eiji.
Damn that Ryusuke!
Damn him!
-Good morning.
Hey, Tanaka. I see some
sort of confidence in you lately.
Oh...Really?
Something must have happened.
Is it a girl?
A girl? No, but I have learned
how to do the butterfly kick.
That girl wearing the No. 55 T-shirt
was so cute! A good singer, too!
-Oh, that's Maho-chan!
-Maho?
Come on! Introduce me, will you?!
Nishimoto-sensei is out on maternity leave,
so here is her replacement.
Uh...Ogasawara-sensei!
Hello, everyone!
Uh...I'm Momoko Ogasawara!
I'll be teaching music!
Since we're so close in age,
you can call me Momo-chan!
-Awright!
-Momo-chan!
Man, that substitute is so hot!
"Just call me Momo-tan!"
Hey, Tanaka, are you listening?!
Over there...
Momo-chan!
Uhh, Sensei?
-I feel like giving up teaching.
-Huh?!
After all, no one listens
to me during class...
I was listening! Really listening!
Right, Tanaka?!
I hear you're good at singing, Tanaka-kun!
-Where'd you hear that?
-I heard from Nishimoto-sensei.
This guy can really sing!
The other day, he...
I've been put in charge of the
choir contest for the Culture Festival.
That's great!
I'd like you to lead
the class, Tanaka-kun!
-Eh? T-Tanaka-kun...
-Leading the class?
I'm counting on you!
-Yes, ma'am!
Thank you!
"Music Room"
"Light Music Club"
-If I could have any wish granted now,
-I'd want wings
-Say, isn't the soccer game today?
-I'm supposed to shop with Mariko!
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Come on! This is serious stuff!
-Let's stop by Lotteria.
-Yeah!
Momoko-sensei made this printout
for us! Let's memorize the lyrics-
You're annoying. If you wanna
do this, why not do it yourself?
Everyone...Let's practice harder tomorrow!
-What a ditz!
-Who has time for this?
I'll be waiting for you!
I'll be waiting!
Man, that was scary.
If Hyodo sets his sights on you,
you're in serious trouble.
If you go up against him, you're dead!
Hey! Koyuki!
Izumi-chan!
Did you hear? Ryusuke-kun's
new band finally has a name!
His new band?
Would you believe...it's Beck!
-His dog?
-Oh, that weird dog?
Chiba-kun had the bright idea!
He thought up all kinds of weird names
like Blue Lightning, Naked Devils,
and Dream Travelers.
-Get real!
-It's true!
You want to join the Light Music Club?
Maybe you shouldn't.
Why not? I thought I might make
some friends I can talk music with.
But I haven't heard
anything good about that club.
I haven't heard a thing, either.
"Music Room"
"Light Music Club"
"Cultural Festival"
"One Day Left"
Do you think we'll be ready
in time for the festival tomorrow?
We'll make sure we are.
Think our coffee shop will make money?
No, let's offer curry!
To think that no one's
practicing for tomorrow...
A Jaguar!
And you know...
-Tanaka!
-Whattaya think you're doing?!
-I'm sorry!
-I'll slap you upside your head!
But...This is a Jaguar, right?
A Jaguar like the one
Kurt Cobain of Nirvana used.
-I've always wanted to play-
-Try playing it.
You're sure?
What's with your playing?!
Man, I can't stop laughing!
My sides hurt!
Listen. How long've you been playing?
Well, uh...since summer break.
I'm learning from a man named Saito-san.
He loves British rock.
Who the heck is Saito?
If you learn from a nobody like him
you'll always be the butt of jokes.
You can laugh at me all you like!
But could you stop insulting Saito-san?!
Huh?!
You're a pain, you know? Damn you!
Hey, Tanaka...Do you know
whose Jaguar that is?
It wasn't my fault.
-He's about to start one behind the school!
-Start one?
Hey, Tanaka. I'll introduce
the owner of that Jaguar.
What can I do? I don't
have what I don't have.
-That guy...
-It's Yonehara-sempai.
No one could beat him
when he was in elementary school.
D-don't tell me that was his guitar?
Screw you!
Don't take me for a fool!
That's Rikiya Kitazawa...
my childhood friend.
Whoa...
That fight was over money
borrowed for video games.
-Huh?!
-Which means...
What do you think'll happen
if he finds out about his Jaguar?
Huh?
Hey, Masaru! You were watching?
No, we just happened by.
Oh...Is that so?
"A 14-year-old middle school student,
tired of being bullied at school,
used a tri-sectional staff from China and..."
I didn't tell Rikiya-kun about you, for now.
Koyuki!
Oh...So it is you.
What's wrong? You look pale.
Yeah...But I'm fine now!
Aren't you sweating a lot?
Ryusuke's in a recording studio right now.
Oh, with Beck?
Yeah...Won't you come watch with me?
But...He never wanted to see me again...
Koyuki, are you hungry?
I, uh, treated someone earlier,
so I'm broke...
Want some fries?
Oh, uh...Thanks...
-Want a hamburger too?
-Yeah!
Hurry up, will you?! Come on!
Koyuki!
I'll just take a peek from here.
You serious?
-Oh, that bassist-!
-Yeah. Taira-kun joined up.
Seems Ryusuke and Eiji
went head to head over it.
He did?
Everyone looked all over for a drummer,
but in the end they settled
on Togo-san of Serial Mama.
Oh...That guy?
They've been composing new songs,
auditioning at live houses,
and sending out demo tapes.
I've never seen Ryusuke so pumped up.
Koyuki? What's wrong?
I'm sorry!
Koyuki?!
I've gotta do something, too!
Tanaka-kun?
Momoko-sensei!
It's finally time for the choir contest!
I'm sorry I wasn't able to
live up to your expectations...
Nonsense...
Tanaka-kun...Thank you.
Huh?
Let's sing with all our heart!
Sensei...
Right!
The 8th graders will sing "Give me Wings."
-If I could have any wish granted now,
-I'd want wings
Man...I didn't think we'd be that bad.
We came in last...
and Momoko-sensei cried...
Is that a guitar?
What is this?!
They're having a wild time!
Oh! Look at all those girls!
That guitar...
-It's Hyodo!
-You're right!
Next year, let's do a concert...
Hyodo-kun...He's really good!
Hey...Tanaka.
Hyodo-kun!
Your live performance was great!
I was practicing an imaginary guitar!
Go and buy me a cola, soy milk,
a melon roll, and a curry bun.
Your encore was so exciting!
Even Kazuko-sensei was dancing!
Bring them to the music room ASAP.
I ran into Rikiya-kun earlier.
He was steaming
about the scratch on the Jaguar.
He's searching all over
for the one who did it.
T-that last song was
a cover of Springs, right?!
Listen! I don't wanna talk music with you!
If you don't want me to tell
Rikiya-kun about the scratch,
you'd better hurry up and do as I say!
Screw that...He can't order me around.
Hey! Rikiya-sempai's started a fight!
Hey, isn't that the Judo Club captain?!
I'm in a bad mood today!
Don't complain just because
I skipped the room-cleaning!
Koyuki!
Melon roll, curry bun, cola, soy milk!
Melon roll? Weird...
"Fishing Hole"
This is bad! This goes
beyond being just a prank!
Let's report it to the police!
I know who did it.
Eiji?
Yeah...
The day the Les Paul was stolen,
I saw his car, too.
Damn! Shall we go and pulverize his Strat?!
Lucille.
-Huh?
Lucille's the only one left.
Lucille?
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Maybe I'll take a trip to where
the dropped pencil points.
"Next Episode"
"Lucille"
Maybe I'll take a trip to where
the dropped pencil points.
"Next Episode"
"Lucille"
There's sure to be a dream lying there!